ROHINI MOHANDOSS

SUMMARY CONTACT

I am a passionate UX Designer with a background in web design and development. I invoke user delight by creating useful and usable user experiences. With the unique combination of skills, I bring method to madness by designing functional and creative UX.

mrohini07@gmail.com (858) 750 - 0282 www.mrohini.com linkedin.com/in/rohini-mohandoss

AWARDS

First place winner - GA Hackathon! Designed a slang translation tool using the Urban Dictionary API. 24 hour project turnaround as an Interaction Designer in a team of 4.

TOOLS & SKILLS

Axure RP Sketch Omnigraffle Adobe XD Photoshop InVision Bootstrap HTML5 CSS3 Javascript JQuery
User Research
Interviewing
Guerilla Testing
Interaction Design

Wireframing Prototyping Usability Testing

EXPERIENCE

JOE COFFEE

FREELANCE UX DESIGNER Seattle, WA Jan 2017 – Feb 2017 Joe Coffee is a startup based in Seattle. I helped them design a mobile app by conducting stakeholder interviews, user interviews, research and usability testing. I proposed elegant solutions through wireframes and hi-fidelity mockups that met business needs and helped improve the user experience in the app.

CDK GLOBAL

(formely an ADP Company), WEB DESIGN SPECIALIST Seattle, WA Sept 2012 – Nov 2016 Developed websites for auto dealers like GM, Lexus and BMW, using CDK's content management system. I focused on not just meeting customer requirements but also helping them by advocating good design practices. This resulted in high quality deliverables. In addition, I worked as a cross team liaison, bridging communication gaps across multiple teams.

KRISANDKATE.COM

WEB DESIGN INTERN
Mercer Island, WA
Mar 2012 – Sept 2012

I was responsible for creating/editing graphics using Photoshop. Using Magento (an eCommerce platform), I created new products and configured content to display in the front-end. Prioritized tasks to meet daily deadlines for the "deal of the day" page.

EDUCATION

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

Seattle, WA Nov 2016 – Current

User Experience Design Immersive program

Full-time Immersive UX Design program that included 500+ hours of professional training over 10 weeks. Hands on experience in User Research, Interaction Design, Prototyping and Usability Testing. Developed skills in design thinking, working in Agile environment, collaborating across teams and client relations.

BELLEVUE COLLEGE

Bellevue, WA May 2010 – Aug 2012

Certificate in Web Design

Proficient in HTML,CSS, Javascript, Photoshop & Dreamweaver. Built a website for Quest Holidayz, a travel agency for the capstone project.

ANNA UNIVERSITY

Tamilnadu, India Aug 2002 – Jun 2006

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Science

Learned the basics for Computer Science and Engineering including Operating systems, Databases and Computer Architecture.